<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on carlos.bz</title><link>https://carlos.bz/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on carlos.bz</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://carlos.bz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On social media</title><link>https://carlos.bz/posts/on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlos.bz/posts/on-social-media/</guid><description>&lt;p>I don’t do social media. Ever.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the past, there were some periods (weeks/months) when I tried being active on social media, just to see if I could get something positive out of it. Who knows? No. Mistake. It didn’t work out that way. It was a disaster. It’s not for me.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I felt completely manipulated and overwhelmed, stuck in a cycle I didn’t want to be part of. On top of that, I considered it a complete waste of time, even counterproductive, since it can feed into your insecurities. Am I getting fewer likes? Oh no, what will become of me?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Coordinates</title><link>https://carlos.bz/posts/coordinates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlos.bz/posts/coordinates/</guid><description>&lt;p>It could be any ordinary Saturday at the beginning of the year. It’s 10:34 PM, and I’m playing my PS5 in the living room with the volume low and a blanket draped over me. I glance around and see shelves filled with books and vinyl records, and nearby, on the dining table, my two black cats resting peacefully. One of them comes to curl up on my lap while I play, and his brother, the shyer one, follows suit a few minutes later.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello</title><link>https://carlos.bz/posts/hello/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlos.bz/posts/hello/</guid><description>&lt;p>I hope you&amp;rsquo;re liking my website.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Expect more &lt;strong>content&lt;/strong> here. I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing from time to time about topics I&amp;rsquo;m interested on, like technology, literature, gaming, philosophy, science and coding.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for reading. 😙&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>